{"data":[{"question":"Found in all parts of the state, pines are the most ordinary trees in Georgia.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Found ","b":"the state","c":"pines are ","d":"ordinary","answer":"4","explain":"- Ordinary-> widespead\/universal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Predators and parasites share a fundamental characteristic they both survive a the price of others.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"share ","b":"characteristic","c":"they both ","d":"price ","answer":"3","explain":"- They both-> they all","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The railroad contributed to the industrial growth not only by connecting these major centers, but also by themselves consume enormous amounts of fuel, iron, and coal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"themselves ","b":"consume ","c":"amounts of ","d":"fuel","answer":"2","explain":"- Consume-> consuming","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The increased urban population was nourished by the increased farm production that, in turn, was made more productive by the use of the new farm machine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was nourished by ","b":"increased ","c":"productive ","d":"machine","answer":"4","explain":"- Machine->machinery","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Europe now began to send tides of immigrants from eastern and southern Europe - most of them were originally poor farmers but who settled in American industrial cities.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"from ","b":"them","c":"but who ","d":"settled ","answer":"2","explain":"- Them-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Often when the weather is extremely hot, people have very thirsty but are not terribly hungry.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Often ","b":"have ","c":"but ","d":"terribly ","answer":"2","explain":"- Have-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Pioneers on the plains sometimes living in dugouts, sod rooms cut into hillsides.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"on the ","b":"sometimes ","c":"living ","d":"cut into ","answer":"3","explain":"- Living-> live","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1786 Benjamin Franklin first suggested daylight savings time as a means of cutting down on the consumes of candles.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first suggested ","b":"means ","c":"cutting ","d":"consumes ","answer":"4","explain":"-Consumes-> consumption","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"An extremely dangerous forms of cocaine, crack attacks the nervous system, brain, and body in a sharper fashion than cocaine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"forms ","b":"attacks ","c":"body ","d":"sharper ","answer":"1","explain":"- Forms-> form","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"On February 20, 1962, Friendship T has orbited the Earth in a manned flight that last just under five hours.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has ","b":"a manned ","c":"flight ","d":"last just ","answer":"1","explain":"- Has-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}